{"ocean":[{"level":"1","type":"ocean","question":"I am big and blue. Boats float on me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💧 Fish swim in me."},{"text":"🌊 I have waves."},{"text":"🚢 Boats like to sail on me."}],"options":[{"label":"Sky","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Ocean","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Grass","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"🌍","riddleIcon":"🌊"}},{"level":"2","type":"ocean","question":"I am a colorful star that lives in the sea. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌟 I have five arms."},{"text":"🎨 I can be many colors."},{"text":"🖐️ I look like a star."}],"options":[{"label":"Rock","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Starfish","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Seagull","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"🌍","riddleIcon":"⭐"}},{"level":"3","type":"ocean","question":"I have a shell and I walk very slowly on the ocean floor. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🏠 I carry my house on my back."},{"text":"🐌 I am a very slow animal."},{"text":"🐚 I live in a shell."}],"options":[{"label":"Snail","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Fish","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Seasnail","isCorrect":true}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"🌍","riddleIcon":"🐌"}},{"level":"4","type":"ocean","question":"I'm a big fish with sharp teeth. I like to swim very fast. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦈 People are afraid of me."},{"text":"🐟 I am a type of fish."},{"text":"🦷 I have very sharp teeth."}],"options":[{"label":"Seal","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Shark","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Dolphin","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"🌍","riddleIcon":"🦈"}},{"level":"5","type":"ocean","question":"I jump and play in the sea. I like to click and whistle. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐬 I am a smart animal."},{"text":"🗣️ I can make many sounds."},{"text":"🌊 I swim in the ocean."}],"options":[{"label":"Dolphin","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Whale","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Crab","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"🌍","riddleIcon":"🐬"}},{"level":"6","type":"ocean","question":"I have eight arms and can squirt ink. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐙 I don't have bones."},{"text":"🎨 I can change color."},{"text":"🖐️ I have many arms."}],"options":[{"label":"Turtle","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Octopus","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Eel","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"🌍","riddleIcon":"🐙"}},{"level":"7","type":"ocean","question":"I dig in the sand and walk sideways. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦀 I have a hard shell."},{"text":"🚶 I walk in a funny way."},{"text":"🏖️ I like to be on the beach."}],"options":[{"label":"Crab","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Lobster","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Seaweed","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"🌍","riddleIcon":"🦀"}},{"level":"8","type":"ocean","question":"I am very big and sing songs. I live in the ocean.","hints":[{"text":"🐋 I'm the biggest animal on Earth!"},{"text":"🎶 My songs can be heard far away."},{"text":"🌊 I like to swim deep down."}],"options":[{"label":"Jellyfish","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Whale","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Shrimp","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"🌍","riddleIcon":"🐳"}},{"level":"9","type":"ocean","question":"I am a slow swimmer with a shell on my back. I lay my eggs on the beach.","hints":[{"text":"🐢 I live a long time."},{"text":"🥚 Baby me hatches from an egg!"},{"text":"🌴 I like warm beaches."}],"options":[{"label":"Sea Turtle","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Sea Horse","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Electric Eel","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"🌍","riddleIcon":"🐢"}},{"level":"10","type":"ocean","question":"I float in the water and sting you when you swim near me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💜 I am wobbly and see-through."},{"text":"☢️ I can give you a little zap!"},{"text":"💧 I'm made of mostly water."}],"options":[{"label":"Jellyfish","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Sea cucumber","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Anglerfish","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"ocean","icon":"🌍","riddleIcon":"💜"}}],"food":[{"level":"1","type":"food","question":"I am yellow and yummy. Monkeys like to peel me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💛 I am a fruit."},{"text":"🐒 Monkeys love me!"},{"text":"😊 You can peel my skin off."}],"options":[{"label":"Apple","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Banana","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Grape","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"2","type":"food","question":"I am white and cold. You eat me with a spoon. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"❄️ I am very cold."},{"text":"🥄 You need a spoon to eat me."},{"text":"🥛 I can be many flavors!"}],"options":[{"label":"Bread","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Ice Cream","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Soup","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"3","type":"food","question":"I am round and orange. Rabbits like to eat me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥕 Bunnies like me!"},{"text":"🟠 I am the color of an orange."},{"text":"🌱 I grow in the ground."}],"options":[{"label":"Carrot","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Tomato","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Potato","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"4","type":"food","question":"I am red and juicy. You eat me in summer. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍉 I am big and round."},{"text":"☀️ I am a summer fruit."},{"text":"🔴 I have a red inside."}],"options":[{"label":"Strawberry","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Watermelon","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cherry","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"5","type":"food","question":"I am long and green. You can eat me in a pickle. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥒 I am a vegetable."},{"text":"🥗 I can be found in salads."},{"text":"💚 I turn into a pickle!"}],"options":[{"label":"Broccoli","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cucumber","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pea","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"6","type":"food","question":"I am small and round. I grow in bunches on a vine. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍇 I am often purple or green."},{"text":"🧺 I grow in a bunch"},{"text":"🍷 Juice can be made from me."}],"options":[{"label":"Pea","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Grape","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Blueberry","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"7","type":"food","question":"I am made of milk. You can spread me on bread. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥛 I come from a cow"},{"text":"🍞 I go well on toast."},{"text":"💛 I can be salted or unsalted."}],"options":[{"label":"Honey","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Butter","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Jam","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"8","type":"food","question":"I'm a drink that comes from a cow. I help you grow big and strong. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐄 I come from an animal."},{"text":"🦴 I make your bones strong"},{"text":"🥛 I am often white."}],"options":[{"label":"Juice","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Milk","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Water","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"9","type":"food","question":"I am orange and sweet. I grow on a tree and have a pit inside. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍑 I am a stone fruit."},{"text":"🌳 I grow on a tree."},{"text":"🟠 My color is similar to an orange"}],"options":[{"label":"Apple","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Orange","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Peach","isCorrect":true}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"10","type":"food","question":"I am brown and crunchy. You can dip me in milk. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥣 I am often eaten for breakfast."},{"text":"🍪 Some people put chocolate chips inside me."},{"text":"🥛 I taste good with milk!"}],"options":[{"label":"Crackers","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cookie","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pretzel","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}}]}